

Adeoye Ajarat Abisola

Web Developer

Profile

I am a dedicated and experienced web developer with a strong foundation in both front-end and back-end development. My journey in the world of web development has been marked by a commitment to excellence and a relentless pursuit of innovation. I am very hardworking and I love learning new things. I like to make new connections and friendships. Coding is my Love Language.

Professional Experience

Web developer, Staff 2023 – present

Lagos, Nigeria

Web developer at Savvynet Technology, Student 2022 - 2023

Back-End Development

Version Control

Lagos, Nigeria

Education

Bachelor of Technology, Ondo State University Science and Technoloy

2018 - present Ondo State, Nigeria

First School Leaving Certificate, Community High School

2012 - 2017 Oyo State, Nigeria

Skills

Frond-End Development

HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, React Node.js, Express.js

Database Management

SQL, MongoDB Git, GitHub

Responsive Design

Deployment & Hosting Bootstrap, CSS Grid, Flexbox Heroku, Netlify, Rectify

Certificates

Savvynet Technology

Giit Africa

Fullstack-Developer

Fullstack-Developer